Find the Cat Bureau.
找猫咪事务所
Never heard of a Cat Bureau.
从没听过什么猫咪事务所啊 ​
Look for a large white cat.
找一只大白猫
This was a pleasant voice, maybe the white cat would be nice too.
那声音很好听   所以也许那只大白猫也会很友善吧
Mm, that was one long weird day.
嗯 真是漫长诡异的一天
I definitely need a break.
我真的得歇一歇了
Mm!
呃
Ah... Oh, what in the heck was that?!
啊    噢  这到底是什么鬼东西啊
Hey, you big fatso. You cats keep freaking me out.
喂    你这只大肥猫   你们这些猫快把我逼疯了
Ah? Are you the big white cat? Are you?
啊   你是那只大白猫吗      是你吗
Listen, cat. I need to know where the Cat Bureau is.
听着   猫咪   请告诉我猫咪事务所的地址
A voice told me to ask you.
有一个声音叫我来问你的
Hmm, must have the wrong person.
嗯   貌似我找错人了
I mean cat, I have the wrong cat.
我是说   找错猫了
Sorry that I sat on you.
不好意思啊   刚刚坐你身上了
Wait, I'll show you.
等等   我带你去
It's him!
真是他
Wait a minute. Slow down!
等等    慢点
Isn't there an easier way?
就没有好走点儿的路吗
Hey, hey come on!
嘿   喂   等等